A Guide to the Fielding Dawson Papers 1978.0003
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series I. Writings
  - Reviews and Criticism
    - Passage of Arms (Box 7)
    - The Perfect Fiction (Box 7)
    - Donald Phelps: Character and Concept (Box 7)
    - Pieces (Box 7)
    - A Poem by Kirby Congdon, A Construction by Jay Socin (Box 7)
    - Pop, or, Feeling-tone Art (Box 7)
    - Portnoy's Complaint (Box 7)
    - Prose Today (Box 7)
    - Rabbit Run (Box 7)
    - Recollections of Gran Apacheria (Box 7)
    - Rothko: A Retrospective Exhibition (Box 7)
    - Season at Coole (Box 7)
    - Six Pack (Box 7)
    - Sketches to Six Writers (Box 7)
    - The Sky Changes (Box 7)
    - Soldier (Box 7)
    - Splendide Hotel (Box 7)
    - Stomping the Goyim (Box 7)
    - Success (Box 7)
    - The Summer Before the Dark (Box 7)
    - Tatlin: Six Stories by Guy Davenport (Box 7)
    - A Thorn in the Dark (Box 7)
    - Tribute to Charles Olson (Box 7)
    - Mexican Memoirs (Box 7)
    - The Unfolding (Box 7)
    - Various Books (2 folders) (Box 7)
    - Views of a Nearsighted Cannoneer (Box 7)
    - West Side Story (Box 7)
    - Which Hand Holds the Brother (Box 7)
    - The Windup (Box 7)
    - YA, & John-Juan (Box 7)
    - You and Me, Essays, etc. by Seymour Krim (Box 7)
  - Screenplay
    - In Memory (4 folders) (Box 7)
  - Published Copies of Works
    - A memoir of Louis Zukofsky (Box 7)
    - A Visit with deKooning (Box 7)
    - Artwork, in Vogue (Box 7)
    - Down Memory Lane (Box 7)
    - End of a Dream (Box 7)
    - Entelechy One (Box 7)
    - Fragments from the Black Mountain Book, in Bazaar (Box 7)
    - The High and the Mighty (Box 7)
    - In Flanders' Field (Box 7)
    - The King and the Burning Boy, in Bazaar (Box 7)
    - Manhatten Crackup 2 (Box 7)
    - The Man with Three Names (Box 7)
    - On Writing Novels (Box 7)
    - Slouching Toward the Stars (Box 7)
    - From Two Penny Lane (Box 7)
    - unidentified story, in Sparrow 26 (Box 7)
    - What Happened Once in Johnny Romero's (Box 7)
    - Word is Consciousness (Box 7)
  - Fragments and Miscellaneous
    - Anthropology Notes (Box 8)
    - Manuscripts (3 folders) (Box 8)
    - Miscellaneous (7 folders) (Box 8)
    - Notes (Box 8)
    - papers from folder marked "criticism" (3 folders) (Box 8)
- Series II. Correspondence
  Series II, CORRESPONDENCE, is the most extensive series in the collection. It includes both incoming and outgoing letters. Five divisions have been created: correspondence circa 1950-1984, letters to mother 1949-1953, letters from mother 1953-1983, letters from family and childhood friends, and miscellaneous letters. These divisions follow an alphabetical scheme as well. Correspondence with several famous individuals will be found in this series. For example, there are letters from politicians like Robert Kennedy and Jacob Javits, and literary figures, like Louis Zukofksy, Charles Olson, and Robert Creeley. Most of the letters are still retained in their original envelopes.
  - Correspondence, 1950-1984
    - Assorted A, 1950-1977 (Box 9)
    - Assorted A, 1977-1980 (Box 9)
    - Abbott, Ward, 1966-1969 (Box 9)
    - Abrams, Sam, 1965-1975 (Box 9)
    - Acker, Kathy, 1973 (Box 9)
    - Alpert, Barry, 1972-1973 (Box 9)
    - Alpert, Barry, 1973-1975, 1977 (Box 9)
    - Amussen, Robert, 1977-1980 (Box 9)
    - Attwell, E.T. [Mr. & Mrs.], 1972-1973 (Box 9)
    - Augustine, Jane, 1973 (Box 9)
    - Assorted B, 1953-1977 (Box 9)
    - Assorted B, 1977-1980 (Box 9)
    - Banks, Russell, 1970-1971 (Box 9)
    - Baracks, Barbara, 1974 (Box 9)
    - Baron, Robert, 1972 (Box 9)
    - Barrone, Dennis, 1976 (Box 9)
    - Baumbach, Jonathan, 1974 (Box 9)
    - Bayes, Ron, 1974-1975 (Box 9)
    - Beck, Claudia, 1976-1977, 1980 (Box 9)
    - Beinings, Guy, 1978 (Box 9)
    - Berge, Carol, 1966-1972 (Box 9)
    - Berge, Carol, 1973-1976, undated (Box 9)
    - Berge, Carol, 1976-1977 (Box 9)
    - Berkson, Bill, 1973-1976 (Box 9)
    - Berkson, Bill, 1980 (Box 9)
    - Berrigan, Sandy, 1964, 1972 (Box 9)
    - Bertholf, Robert, 1973 (Box 9)
    - Bertholf, Robert, 1973 (Box 9)
    - Bertholf, Robert, 1974 (Box 9)
    - Bertholf, Robert, 1974-1976 (Box 9)
    - Bertholf, Robert, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
    - Bertolino, James, 1975 (Box 9)
    - Black Sparrow, 1976-1984 (Box 9)
    - Blaser, Robin (Box 9)
    - B'nai Birth, 1981 (Box 9)
    - Bobbs-Merrill, 1971-1976 (Bin 9)
    - Bohe, Linda, 1977 (Box 9)
    - Book Project (Ivan Perry), 1977 (Box 9)
    - Bourjaily, Vance, 1972 (Box 9)
    - Bowering, George, 1963-1976 (Box 9)
    - Brakhage, Stan, 1975 (Box 9)
    - Brakhage, Stan, 1976-1977 (Box 9)
    - Bresmer, Ray, 1973 (Box 9)
    - Brennan, Patrick, 1974-1975 (Box 9)
    - Brigham, Besmilr, 1967-1973 (Box 9)
    - Brock, Alice, 1970-1972 (Box 9)
    - Brody, Selma, 1969-1977 (Box 9)
    - Bromeridge, David, 1973, 1975 (Box 9)
    - Brotherson, Gordon, 1975 (Box 9)
    - Bruce, Lennart, 1967-1968 (Box 9)
    - Bryan, Tom, 1977-1982 (Box 9)
    - Bultman, Fritz, 1964-1972 (Box 9)
    - Burnaby Art Gallery, 1976 (Box 9)
    - Burns, James, 1977 (Box 9)
    - Burns, James, 1977-1981 (Box 9)
    - Burns, Tarence, 1973 (Box 9)
    - Butterick, George, 1973-1977 (Box 9)
    - Byars, Dorothy, 1969-1980 (Box 9)
    - Byars, Fielding, 1976-1977 (Box 9)
    - Assorted C, 1963-1972 (Box 9)
    - Assorted C, 1973-1977 (Box 9)
    - Assorted C, 1977-1980 (Box 9)
    - Cadigan, George, 1972-1973 (Box 9)
    - Calhoun, Douglas, 1970-1972 (Box 9)
    - Callahan, Bob, 1977 (Box 9)
    - Callas, Max, 1967-1970 (Box 9)
    - Capilano Review, 1976-1979 (Box 9)
    - Caplan, Ron, 1964 (Box 9)
    - Casement, Douglas (The Sparrow), 1964 (Box 9)
    - Chaloner, David, 1980 (Box 9)
    - Chamberlin, Elaine, 1971 (Box 9)
    - Chapin, Hank, 1963-1964 (Box 9)
    - Charles Scribner & Sons Inc., 1960 (Box 9)
    - Chester, Laura, 1973-1977 (Box 9)
    - Chester, Laura, 1979 (Box 9)
    - Chicago Review, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
    - Clare, Josephine, 1976-1977 (Box 9)
    - Clark, Joseph, 1971 (Box 9)
    - Clark, Nancy, 1973-1975 (Box 9)
    - Clark, Tom, 1960-1972 (Box 9)
    - Clarke, Jack (Sand Dollar), 1978-1982 (Box 9)
    - Clayton, Charles, 1972-1976 (Box 9)
    - Coleman, Victor, 1976-1977 (Box 9)
    - Coleman, Victor, 1977-1980 (Box 9)
    - Compendium Books, 1971-1976 (Box 9)
    - Contemporary Books, 1975 (Box 9)
    - Coolidge, Clark, 1964-1965, 1973 (Box 9)
    - Coolidge, Clark, 1973-1976 (Box 9)
    - Creative Artists Public Service Programs, 1973-1975 (Box 9)
    - Creeley, Bob, 1955-1956 (Box 9)
    - Creeley, Bob, 1956-1969 (Box 9)
    - Creeley, Bob (distinction made by Fielding), 1962-1977 (Box 9)
    - Crozier, Andrew, 1964-1965 (Box 9)
    - Crozier, Andrew, 1966-1973 (Box 9)
    - Crozier, Andrew, 1973-1977 (Box 9)
    - Crozier, Andrew, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
    - Crozier, Harold, 1976-1977 (Box 9)
    - Cufton, Merritt, 1979 (Box 10)
    - Curtis, C. Michael, 1968-1977 (Box 10)
    - Assorted D, 1960-1977 (Box 10)
    - Assorted D, 1978-1979, 1985 (Box 10)
    - Daley, John, 1974-1975 (Box 10)
    - Daley, John, 1976-1977 (Box 10)
    - Daley, John, 1977-1980 (Box 10)
    - Dart, Charles [Dr.], 1973, 1975 (Box 10)
    - Davenport, Guy, 1971 (Box 10)
    - Davidson, Michael, 1971, 1975 (Box 10)
    - Davies, Alan, 1974-1975 (Box 10)
    - Dawson, Barbara, 1968, 1976-1977 (Box 10)
    - Dawson, Barbara, 1977-1978 (Box 10)
    - Dawson, Fielding (outgoing), 1959-1977 (Box 10)
    - Dawson, Fielding to Max Finstein, 1962-1965 (Box 10)
    - Dawson, Fielding to Howard McCord, 1971-1973 (Box 10)
    - Dawson, Fielding, outgoing, 1951-1984 (Box 10)
    - Dean, Nick, 1974 (Box 10)
    - DeAnza College, 1975-1976 (Box 10)
    - December (magazine), 1971 (Box 10)
    - DeHaren, Tom, 1972 (Box 10)
    - Deloach, Allen, 1974-1975 (Box 10)
    - Destaebler, Stephen, 1949-1951 (Box 10)
    - Destaebler, Stephen, 1951-1952 (Box 10)
    - Destaebler, Stephen, 1976 (Box 10)
    - Dial Press, 1971 (Box 10)
    - DiPrima, Diane, 1964 (Box 10)
    - Donnavan, Cara, 1976-1977 (Box 10)
    - Dorn, Ed, 1963-1966, 1973 (Box 10)
    - Dorn, Ed, 1974-1976 (Box 10)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1964-1969 (Box 10)
    - Assorted E, 1969-1977 (Box 10)
    - Assorted E, 1977-1980 (Box 10)
    - Emelau, Bill, 1974-1975 (Box 10)
    - Early, Joe, 1971-1974 (Box 10)
    - Eastman, Julie, 1956-1961 (Box 10)
    - Eastman, Julie, 1967-1970 (Box 10)
    - Eastman, Julie, 1972-1975 (Box 10)
    - Eastman, Julie, 1978, undated (Box 10)
    - Edson, Pat, 1950 (Box 10)
    - Emerson, Steve, 1975-1976 (Box 10)
    - Empire State College, 1974-1975 (Box 10)
    - Eshelman, Clayton, 1970-1975 (Box 10)
    - Esquire, 1960, 1971, undated (Box 10)
    - Eulert, Don, 1971 (Box 10)
    - Eureka Review, 1975 (Box 10)
    - Assorted F, 1951-1977 (Box 10)
    - Assorted F, 1977-1984 (Box 10)
    - Fagin, Larry, 1973 (Box 10)
    - Feld, Ross, 1980 (Box 10)
    - Fick, Jorge, 1953-1964 (Box 10)
    - Field, Sherry, 1974-1975 (Box 10)
    - Fink, Lawrence, 1970-1972 (Box 10)
    - Finstein, Max, 1959-1965 (Box 10)
    - Finstein, Max, 1966-1975 (Box 10)
    - Fiore, Joe, 1953-1968 (Box 10)
    - Fiore, Joe, 1978, undated (Box 10)
    - Fiore, Mary, 1979-1984 (Box 10)
    - Fischer, Cara, 1978-1984 (Box 10)
    - Fischer, Cara, 1984 (Box 10)
    - Fredonia College, 1975 (Box 10)
    - Friedman, B.H., 1972-1973 (Box 10)
    - Assorted G, 1950-1977 (Box 10)
    - Assorted G, 1978-1984 (Box 10)
    - Gafford, Charlotte, 1972-1973 (Box 10)
    - Gafford, Charlotte, 1974-1975 (Box 10)
    - Garraty, John (Columbia University), 1972 (Box 10)
    - Gelpi, Albert, 1975 (Box 10)
    - Gifford, Barry, 1970-1976 (Box 10)
    - Gilliard, Suzanne, 1978-1980 (Box 10)
    - Gilson, Melvina, 1977-1979 (Box 10)
    - Gitin, David & Marcia, 1975-1976 (Box 10)
    - Glotzer, David (Mulch Press), 1974-1975 (Box 10)
    - Goldman, Frank, 1974-1975 (Box 10)
    - Goodell, Larry, 1964-1970 (Box 10)
    - Goodman, Paul, 1950-1951 (Box 10)
    - Gotham Book Mart, 1970 (Box 10)
    - Grad, Wendy, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
    - Green, Galen, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
    - Griffith, Sheila, 1970-1977 (Box 10)
    - Grosshans, Katherine, 1976 (Box 10)
    - Grossinger, Richard, 1971-1977 (Box 10)
    - Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1979 (Box 10)
    - Guston, Phillip, 1975 (Box 10)
    - Assorted H, 1950-1977 (Box 11)
    - Assorted H (Box 11)
    - Hachman, Neil, 1974 (Box 11)
    - Hallberg, Bill, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
    - Hamilton, Jim, 1974-1975 (Box 11)
    - Harlow, Enid, 1969-1976 (Box 11)
    - Harlow, Enid, 1978-1979 (Box 11)
    - Harmon, Harvey, 1950-1971 (Box 11)
    - Harris, Marguerite, 1964 (Box 11)
    - Hawkins, Bobbie Louise, 1974 (Box 11)
    - Hawkins, Bobbie Louise, 1979 (Box 11)
    - Heliezer, Piero, 1961-1970 (Box 11)
    - Hemensley, Kris, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
    - Hemensley, Kris, 1977 (Box 11)
    - Henderson, David (Box 11)
    - Henderson, J., 1971 (Box 11)
    - Henry, Terry (Old Marble Press), 1974 (Box 11)
    - Herd, Dale, 1976-1977 (Box 11)
    - Herd, Dale, 1977 (Box 11)
    - Herkert, Joe, 1971-1976 (Box 11)
    - Herkert, Joe, 1977-1980 (Box 11)
    - Herridon, Jim, 1956-1971 (Box 11)
    - Herr, Jeff, 1974, 1976 (Box 11)
    - Higgins, Dick, 1978-1980 (Box 11)
    - Hobbs, Ronald, 1971-1972 (Box 11)
    - Hollo, Anselm, 1972-1976 (Box 11)
    - Hollo, Anselm, 1979 (Box 11)
    - Homire, Cynthia, 1956 (Box 11)
    - Honey, William, 1964-1972 (Box 11)
    - Honey, William, 1973-1977 (Box 11)
    - Hovk, Jeff, 1976 (Box 11)
    - Hubbard, Serena, 1977-1980 (Box 11)
    - Ingham, Charles, 1977 (Box 11)
    - Irby, Kenneth, 1972 (Box 11)
    - Assorted J, 1969-1977 (Box 11)
    - James, John, 1977 (Box 11)
    - Jahts, Jacob, 1977 (Box 11)
    - Jerry, 1971-1975 (Box 11)
    - Joan Scott Inc., 1971 (Box 11)
    - John O'Hara Journal, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
    - Johnson, Paul, 1977 (Box 11)
    - Johnson, Ray, 1973 (Box 11)
    - Johnson, Ron, 1980 (Box 11)
    - Jones, Judith (Alfred Knopf Inc.), 1970, 1973 (Box 11)
    - Jones, Leroi (Totem Press), 1961-1963 (Box 11)
    - Jones, Whitney, 1975-1977 (Box 11)
    - Jones, Whitney, 1978 (Box 11)
    - Julia, ca. 1968 (Box 11)
    - Assorted K, 1967-1977 (Box 11)
    - Assorted K, 1977-1983 (Box 11)
    - Kaiser, Betty, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Kalos, Victor, 1952-1956 (Box 11)
    - Kaspar, John, 1951-1952 (Box 11)
    - Keeble, John, 1976 (Box 11)
    - Kelly, Robert, 1963-1971 (Box 11)
    - Kelman, Jim, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
    - Kennedy, Robert F., 1966 (Box 11)
    - Kenner, Hugh, 1978 (Box 11)
    - Kimball, George, ca. 1970 (Box 11)
    - King, Basil (Mulch Press), 1959-1970 (Box 11)
    - King, Basil (Mulch Press), 1974-1976 (Box 11)
    - Kirkland College, 1975 (Box 11)
    - Kirkland High School, 1972-1974 (Box 11)
    - Kline, Franz, 1956-1958 (Box 11)
    - Knight, Arthur & Glee, 1971-1972 (Box 11)
    - Koehler, Michael, 1974 (Box 11)
    - Kollmar, Richard, 1977-1978 (Box 11)
    - Kremen, Irwin, 1979 (Box 11)
    - Krim, Seymour, 1969-1976 (Box 11)
    - Krim, Seymour, 1977-1980 (Box 11)
    - Kulchur, 1965 (Box 11)
    - Assorted L, 1955-1977 (Box 11)
    - Assorted L, 1977-1984 (Box 11)
    - Laciny, Ellen, 1970-1977 (Box 11)
    - Laforge, Tim, 1953-1955 (Box 11)
    - Lane, M., 1972 (Box 11)
    - Lane, Mervin, 1977-1983 (Box 11)
    - Lange, Art, 1977-1980 (Box 11)
    - La Palma, Marina, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Laubies, Rene, 1955 (Box 11)
    - Lefford, Arthur, 1972 (Box 11)
    - Lefford, Arthur, 1978 (Box 11)
    - Leibowitz, Herb, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
    - Lessing, Doris, 1967 (Box 11)
    - Levine, Norman, 1976 (Box 11)
    - Lewis, Harold (Mulch Press), 1972-1973 (Box 11)
    - Lewis, Laurie, 1974-1975 (Box 11)
    - Lieber, Edward, 1979 (Box 11)
    - Lish, Gordon (Alfred A. Knopf Inc.), 1977 (Box 11)
    - Loewinsohn, Tim, 1961-1963 (Box 11)
    - Longville, Tim, 1968-1971 (Box 11)
    - Lo-Lo, 1949-1950 (Box 11)
    - Lucas, Tom, 1974-1975 (Box 11)
    - Lurie, Boris, 1970 (Box 11)
    - Assorted M, 1961-1975 (Box 11)
    - Assorted M, 1976-1977 (Box 11)
    - Assorted M, 1977-1982 (Box 11)
    - Maldovan, Helen, 1977-1980, undated (Box 11)
    - Malanga, Gerard, 1977 (Box 11)
    - Mandell, Eli, 1976 (Box 11)
    - Marisol, 1973 (Box 11)
    - Marlatt, Daphine, 1975-1977 (Box 11)
    - Marlatt, Daphine, 1977-1979 (Box 11)
    - Martin, John (Black Sparrow Press), 1967-1970 (Box 11)
    - Martin, John (Black Sparrow Press), 1970 (Box 11)
    - Martin, John (Black Sparrow Press), 1971 (Box 11)
    - Martin, John (Black Sparrow Press), 1972 (Box 11)
    - Martin, John (Black Sparrow Press), 1973 (Box 11)
    - Martin, John (Black Sparrow Press), 1974 (Box 11)
    - Martin, John (Black Sparrow Press), 1975 (Box 11)
    - Martin, John (Black Sparrow Press), 1976 (Box 12)
    - Martin, John (Black Sparrow Press), 1977, undated (Box 12)
    - Martin, John (Black Sparrow Press), 1977-1980 (Box 12)
    - Martin, John (Black Sparrow Press), 1981-1984 (Box 12)
    - Marshall, Thomas, 1974-1975 (Box 12)
    - Marz, Verlag, 1970 (Box 12)
    - Mathers, Wendy, 1978-1979 (Box 12)
    - Mattingly, George, 1978-1980 (Box 12)
    - Mayers, Daivid and Diane, 1975-1977 (Box 12)
    - McCord, Howard, 1971-1972 (Box 12)
    - McCord, Howard, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
    - McCord, Howard, 1974-1976 (Box 12)
    - McCracken, John, 1974-1976 (Box 12)
    - McDonough, Patrick, 1972 (Box 12)
    - McNaughton, Patrick, 1976 (Box 12)
    - Meanor, P., 1976 (Box 12)
    - Melham, D.H., 1977 (Box 12)
    - Melvina, 1970-1973 (Box 12)
    - Maserli, Douglas, 1975-1976 (Box 12)
    - Maserli, Douglas, 1978 (Box 12)
    - Metcalf, Paul, 1973-1975 (Box 12)
    - Micheline, Jack, 1964-1974 (Box 12)
    - Mitchell, Burroughs, 1972 (Box 12)
    - Montgomery, Stuart, 1965 (Box 12)
    - Moore, Frank, 1951 (Box 12)
    - Morehead, M., 1976 (Box 12)
    - Morfopoulds, Ricky, 1977-1979, undated (Box 12)
    - Morley, Hilda, 1973 (Box 12)
    - Morris, Micahel, 1976 (Box 12)
    - Morris, Richard (Camel's Coming Publishing), 1965-1973 (Box 12)
    - Morris, Wright, 1971 (Box 12)
    - Morrow, Bradford, 1978 (Box 12)
    - Moskowitz, Hermine, 1956, 1965 (Box 12)
    - Motherwell, Bob, 1965-1967 (Box 12)
    - Mottram, Eric, 1974 (Box 12)
    - Mudborn Press, 1975-1977 (Box 12)
    - Mudborn Press, 1978 (Box 12)
    - Mulford, Wendy, 1978 (Box 12)
    - Assorted N, 1959-1975 (Box 12)
    - Assorted N, 1976, 1978 (Box 12)
    - Naropa Institute, 1979 (Box 12)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1973-1975 (Box 12)
    - Nations, Opaland Ellen, 1977 (Box 12)
    - Nelson, Pat, 1953-1956 (Box 12)
    - New American Review, 1970, 1972 (Box 12)
    - New South Writing, 1974 (Box 12)
    - New Story, 1973 (Box 12)
    - New Yorker, 1971, undated (Box 12)
    - Newman, Robert, 1979 (Box 12)
    - Niederman, Fred, 1973-1976 (Box 12)
    - Noland, Ken & Neil, 1953-1965 (Box 12)
    - Assorted O, 1965-1975 (Box 12)
    - O'Connor, Phillip, 1972-1973 (Box 12)
    - Olsen, Debbie, 1974-1975 (Box 12)
    - Olson, Charles, ca. 1950s (Box 12)
    - Olson, Charles, ca. 1950s (Box 12)
    - Ontario Review, 1974-1975 (Box 12)
    - Oppenheimer, Joel, 1953, 1977 (Box 12)
    - Assorted P, 1950-1977 (Box 12)
    - Assorted P, 1979-1982 (Box 12)
    - Padgett, Ron, 1964 (Box 12)
    - Painter, Charlotte, 1971-1976 (Box 12)
    - Pan, Pola, 1977 (Box 12)
    - Pantheon Books, 1967-1974 (Box 12)
    - Parrot, Jerry (RAIN), 1971 (Box 12)
    - Partisan Review, 1972-1973 (Box 12)
    - Patterson, Tom, 1975-1977 (Box 12)
    - Patterson, Tom, 1978-1980 (Box 12)
    - Pearlman, Bill, 1971-1975 (Box 12)
    - P.E.N. American Center, 1975-1977 (Box 12)
    - P.E.N. American Center, 1979 (Box 12)
    - Perelman, Bob, 1975 (Box 12)
    - Perry, Ginger, 1979-1980 (Box 12)
    - Peterson, Will, 1973 (Box 12)
    - Peterson, Will, 1974 (Box 12)
    - Peterson, Will, 1975 (Box 12)
    - Peterson, Will, 1977 (Box 12)
    - Peyster, Steven (Black Sparrow Press), 1975-1977 (Box 12)
    - Peyster, Steven (Black Sparrow Press), 1977-1980 (Box 12)
    - Phelps, Donald, 1965-1972 (Box 12)
    - Philips, Dorothy, 1974-1976 (Box 12)
    - Pittis, A.D., 1964-1977 (Box 12)
    - Pittis, A.D., 1978-1980 (Box 12)
    - Plucked Chicken, 1977 (Box 12)
    - Poets and Writers, 1971-1975 (Box 12)
    - Poets and Writers, 1976-1977 (Box 12)
    - Pohl, M., 1971, undated (Box 12)
    - Pohl, Frederick, 1974 (Box 12)
    - Pollman, L.R. (Fernand), 1961-1971 (Box 12)
    - Pommy-Vega, Janine, 1977 (Box 12)
    - Ponzin, Tom, 1972-1976 (Box 12)
    - Porter, T.E. (The Falcon), 1973-1975 (Box 12)
    - Porter, T.E. (The Falcon), 1975-1977 (Box 12)
    - Porter, T.E. (The Falcon), 1977-1980 (Box 12)
    - Powell, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
    - Powell, Dan, 1979-1980 (Box 12)
    - Quasha, George, 1980 (Box 12)
    - Queen, Claudia, 1974-1976 (Box 12)
    - Assorted R, 1954-1976 (Box 12)
    - Assorted R, 1978-1980 (Box 12)
    - Randall, Margaret, 1962-1965 (Box 12)
    - Raworth, Tom, 1961-1965 (Box 12)
    - Raworth, Tom, 1965-1977 (Box 12)
    - Ray, David, 1975 (Box 12)
    - Reed, Ishmel, 1971 (Box 12)
    - Reid, Ed, 1977-1980 (Box 12)
    - Reid, Gene, 1953-1956 (Box 12)
    - Rice, Barbara, 1970-1973 (Box 13)
    - Rice, Caitlin, 1970 (Box 13)
    - Rice, Caitlin, 1979 (Box 13)
    - Rice, Dan, 1953-1971 (Box 13)
    - Rice, Megan, 1970-1976, undated (Box 13)
    - Rice, Megan, 1977-1980 (Box 13)
    - Richards, M.C., 1953 (Box 13)
    - Righthouse, Jim, 1972 (Box 13)
    - Riley, Peter, 1968 (Box 13)
    - Rissman, Marshall (Box 13)
    - Ritchie, Cynthia (Box 13)
    - Rivlin, Michael, 1971-1974 (Box 13)
    - Rodefer, Steve, 1964-1975 (Box 13)
    - Rome, Stuart, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
    - Rosenberg, David, 1968 (Box 13)
    - Rosenberg, Pattie, 1976 (Box 13)
    - Ross, Robert, 1977-1980, undated (Box 13)
    - Rubinoff, Kathy, 1975-1976 (Box 13)
    - Rumaker, Michael, 1965-1977 (Box 13)
    - Assorted S, 1941-1977 (Box 13)
    - Assorted S, 1977-1980 (Box 13)
    - San Francisco Book Review, 1972-1973 (Box 13)
    - Sanders, 1971-1974 (Box 13)
    - Sand Dollar, 1976 (Box 13)
    - Saroyam, Aram, 1963-1965 (Box 13)
    - Sasek, Ed, 1981 (Box 13)
    - Sauls, Roger (New Lazarus Review), 1977 (Box 13)
    - Schaff, David, 1969-1970 (Box 13)
    - Schasberger, Ellen, 1953-1954 (Box 13)
    - Sheard, Sarah, 1977 (Box 13)
    - Sherwin, Judith Johnson, 1976 (Box 13)
    - Shevelon, Kathy, 1974-1975 (Box 13)
    - Shields, William, 1980 (Box 13)
    - Shoemaker, Jack, 1983 (Box 13)
    - Siegel, Fred, 1965-1972 (Box 13)
    - Silberberg, Elliot, 1973-1974 (Box 13)
    - Silliman, Ron, 1975 (Box 13)
    - Simpson, Granny, 1971-1975 (Box 13)
    - Simpson, Granny, 1978 (Box 13)
    - Sinclair, John, 1965-1966 (Box 13)
    - Sixpack, 1974 (Box 13)
    - Skillings, 1973-1974, 1977 (Box 13)
    - Slein, Keith, 1977-1980 (Box 13)
    - Small Publisher's Company, 1971-1972 (Box 13)
    - Socin, Jay, 1962-1963 (Box 13)
    - Soloman, Norman, 1975
    - Solotaroff, Ted (American Review), 1973-1976 (Box 13)
    - Southern, David, 1875-1977 (Box 13)
    - Southern, David, 1977-1979 (Box 13)
    - Stark, Brad, 1969-1975 (Box 13)
    - Stark, Brad, 1978-1980 (Box 13)
    - Stephens, M.G., 1974-1976 (Box 13)
    - Stoehr, Taylor, 1976 (Box 13)
    - Succop, Greg, 1974-1976 (Box 13)
    - Sukenidk, Lynn, 1974-1975 (Box 13)
    - Swartz, Jean, 1973-1974 (Box 13)
    - Sylvester, Bill, 1980 (Box 13)
    - Assorted T, 1955-1977 (Box 13)
    - Assorted T, 1977-1982 (Box 13)
    - Teter, Hollbrook, 1974 (Box 13)
    - Thayer, Carl, 1974 (Box 13)
    - Thibeau, Jack, 1973 (Box 13)
    - Thomas Jefferson College, 1974-1976 (Box 13)
    - Tri-Quarterly, 1975 (Box 13)
    - Turtle Island, 1974-1975 (Box 13)
    - Turtle Island, 1975-1977 (Box 13)
    - University of San Diego, 1978 (Box 13)
    - Assorted V, 1950-1976, undated (Box 13)
    - Vas Dias, Robert, 1977-1979 (Box 13)
    - Vevers, Tony, 1971, 1977-1979 (Box 13)
    - Viking Press, 1976-1979 (Box 13)
    - Viscerally Press, 1979 (Box 13)
    - Assorted W, 1956-1974 (Box 13)
    - Assorted W, 1975-1977, undated (Box 13)
    - Wachtel, Andrea, 1971-1972 (Box 13)
    - Wagner, Charles, 1975-1976, undated (Box 13)
    - Wagnon, Drew, 1964-1965 (Box 13)
    - Wakosil, Diane, 1971 (Box 13)
    - Warsh, Lewis, 1973 (Box 13)
    - Washington State College (Eastern), 1976 (Box 13)
    - Watton, Barry, 1973 (Box 13)
    - Weaver, Mike, 1963, 1967 (Box 13)
    - Weinberger, Tony, 1971-1972 (Box 13)
    - Weinstein, Norman, 1973 (Box 13)
    - Whitaker, T.R., 1974 (Box 13)
    - Who's Who, 1973-1975 (Box 13)
    - Wickoff, Max, 1978 (Box 13)
    - Wilcox, Donna, 1978 (Box 13)
    - Wilding, Michael, 1975-1977 (Box 13)
    - Wilkinson, John, 1977-1979 (Box 13)
    - William Hoffer Bookseller, 1977 (Box 13)
    - Williams, Jonathan, 1953-1954 (Box 13)
    - Williams, Jonathan, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Williams, Jonathan, 1956-1972 (Box 13)
    - Williams, Jonathan, 1973-1975 (Box 13)
    - Williams, Jonathan, 1975-1977 (Box 13)
    - Wilson, Keith, 1976 (Box 13)
    - Wit, Harold, 1970-1974 (Box 13)
    - Wolfe, Tina, 1971-1974 (Box 13)
    - Woods, H., 1975-1976 (Box 13)
    - Woolf, D., 1972 (Box 13)
    - Words, 1980 (Box 13)
    - Wray, Ron, 1977-1978 (Box 13)
    - Wurlitzer, Rudy, 1967-1970 (Box 13)
    - Xavier Fourcade Inc., 1979 (Box 13)
    - Assorted Y, 1971-1977 (Box 13)
    - Assorted Y, 1977-1978 (Box 13)
    - Young, Al, 1976 (Box 13)
    - Young, David, 1973-1974 (Box 13)
    - Young, David, 1975-1977 (Box 13)
    - Young, David, 1978-1980 (Box 13)
    - Assorted Z, 1975, undated (Box 13)
    - Zukofsky, Paul, 1978 (Box 13)
    - Zukofsky, Louis, 1963-1971 (Box 13)
  - Letters to Mother, 1949-1953
    - Letters to mother, 1949 (Box 16)
    - Letters to mother, 1950 (Box 16)
    - Letters to mother, 1951 (Box 16)
    - Letters to mother, 1952 (Box 16)
    - Letters to mother, 1952 (Box 16)